Since 2020, a year of immense
global
change and challenges, Prudential Vietnam has
continued to affirm its commitment to
sustainable growth and effective business operations. We continue to
prioritize actions for the health and
well-being of our customers and
contribute to the development of the
economy, remaining steadfast in our goal of putting customers at the
center of all our activities.
Accordingly, in 2020, Prudential
continued to accelerate the modernization and application of
technology in most insurance services
and improve processes to create a seamless customer
experience at every touchpoint.
All processes from consultation and underwriting to
claims processing were moved to online platforms
with automated processing,
yielding impressive results
while ensuring a
safe and continuous customer experience, even during the
pandemic.
Alongside this, we strive to help everyone
access and apply
advanced healthcare technologies to their
lives, leading to
greater happiness.
During the COVID-19 pandemic,
Prudential launched its Hotspot
Prudential app, a healthcare application
based on Artificial Intelligence, providing
comprehensive health management solutions
for users with features such as
health checks, symptom checks,
online doctor consultations, and many
other outstanding features. This empowers Vietnamese people to proactively
control and care for their physical and mental health
anytime, anywhere. To date, over
4.4 million apps have been downloaded, with several million
registered users, accounting for 1/5 of the
total user base in Asia. In terms of
product offerings, Prudential also researches and
develops many quality insurance solutions
suitable for the diverse protection needs and
financial capabilities of its customers.
Prudential's efforts have received
positive feedback from customers, according to a
survey conducted by 2P&P.
Prudential ranked second in the top 10
best performing brands in 2020 and was the
only foreign insurance company
in this ranking.  By
adapting quickly to changes,
Prudential has achieved efficiency in its
business operations and business performance,
successfully completing its business objectives,
recording stable growth,
and affirming its strong financial potential.
Prudential's total revenue reached
nearly VND 34,000 billion, of which
net revenue from insurance business operations
reached nearly VND 25,000 billion. New premium revenue in
Q5 was approximately VND 5.5 trillion, and
pre-tax profit reached nearly
VND 2.8 trillion. Above all, with its mission to protect the
financial security of over 1.6 million
customers and become a solid shield
against risks, Prudential has paid out over VND
6.7 trillion in insurance benefits to
customers, equivalent to nearly thirty
percent of the total insurance benefits paid out by the
entire life insurance industry in
2020. Simultaneously, it maintains
high liquidity with a solvency margin of nearly 140 percent, demonstrating its
ability to pay out to customers, a
key indicator of its
overall value.  With assets exceeding 124 trillion
VND and total investment in the economy
exceeding 12,000 billion VND, Prudential
also demonstrated strong financial potential
in business and investment in 2020,
recording positive returns from
all its
investment-linked insurance products, which
are currently dominant in the market.
These outstanding business results are proof of Prudential
's long-term commitment to effective operations
in Vietnam and
demonstrate its strong contribution
to the development of the economy. Investing for the
sustainable development of the community is
always a priority for Prudential. In 2020,
Prudential continued to invest in
practical and meaningful activities for the
sustainable development of the community across three
key areas: healthy living, education, and safety. The
total investment budget reached over
205 billion VND
between 2011 and 2020,
built upon solid foundations.  For over two
decades, and going forward,
Prudential is committed to
sustainable growth and fulfilling its mission of protecting
financial security so that customers can
pursue their life goals with complete peace of mind.